Question in the kitchen
Good evening everyone!
I have a question for you in the kitchen.
Today I will answer 100 questions!
Nice to meet you!
Please introduce yourself.
This is Quality in the Kitchen. I am Mr. Sendai.
My member color is green.
My nickname is Pearl. Nice to meet you.
My birthday is June 22, 2003.
It is June 22 of this year.
The world is bad, what are you doing? Well, I don't know what I'm going to do.
But I'll probably read my favorite manga and spend time with my family.
Yakitori, what would you like?
Yakitori, what do you want? Yakitori... what would you like?
But, basically, I like all yakitori.
I order all of them.
Yakitori? That's a great yakitori question.
Tare or salt? Or salt?
Tare!
Do you take the white streaks out of the mandarin oranges?
Well, maybe I should...they're bitter.
What is your favorite hairstyle?
Uh, long black hair.
Do you like spicy food?
Uh-uh.
I don't like it.
What color would you dye your hair?
Uh, black, I guess.
Do you believe in ghosts? I don't believe in ghosts. Yellow? - Uh, black.
Do you believe in spirits? I don't believe in them.
What's your personal favorite food to eat alone?
Uh, rice with... uh, whatever.
Cold yakko? A. Silk or cotton? A. Either is fine, but silk?
Q. What kind of food do you like?
A. Ramen, cardamom, what kind of food do you like?
A.Infinite
Q.What is essential for an expedition?Q.What are the essentials for an expedition?
A.What are the essentials for an expedition? What is essential for an expedition? Well, there are a lot of things, but when I am in the car
What do you call it, a neck warmer?
No, no, no.
Neck pillow.
I take a neck pillow.
Which instrument do you play in a band? I'd have to say the guitar.
I'd eat a baked sweet potato without the skin. I'd eat it.
I eat... A baked sweet potato. What's the last thing you dreamed about?
A dream.
I don't remember.
What is your favorite season? Summer.
That's why I wear short sleeves.
Rice? Bread?
I prefer rice.
What flavor of ramen do you prefer?
Uh, I like them all.
Soy sauce.
Free transportation for life.
Anywhere.
Everywhere.
What's your favorite sushi?
Um... sea urchin.
If you could figure it out, what would it be?
What would you like?
Makiichi Kudo.
Group name?
What? Really?
If you could figure it out, what would it be?
I don't know, maybe "Candy Wavy"?
What's your favorite word?
Q. How does one go from being a bad teacher to an expert? A.The first step is to know how bad you are at it.
Q.Where would you like to go on a trip in Japan? A.Okinawa
Q.Where would you like to go on an overseas trip? I would like to go to the U.S.A.
What do you do on your day off? Well, I stay in bed.
How many meals a day?
I'm eating two meals a day these days.
What is your favorite animal?What is your favorite animal?
Bears and alligators.
What is your favorite lyric or song?
I also like the song "Endless Journey" by Mystil.
What is your favorite word?
Pearl
Do you have a driver's license?
No.
How fast are you in 50m?
50 meters. How fast?
I hate to say it, but probably about 9 seconds.
What's your favorite subject?
Music.
Do you know anyone on your own?
A little bit.
What's your favorite thing?
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Please try it.
Q. If you were to compare yourself with one Chinese character, what would it be?
A. If you were to compare yourself with one Kanji character, what would it be?
A. "Shin" for pearl.
Q. Can you get it out?
A. Yes!
Q. What is your habit? Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha... ummm... what do you think? Oh!
What's your habit?
Uh...
I touch my hair a lot.
What's your favorite TOKUSA song?
I have many favorite TOKUSA songs.
Delusional Equation
What do you think about during a live performance?
What do you think about during the show?
Well, I look at everyone's face.
Q.What is your favorite song to sing live? A.I think "The Deliberate Expert" on purpose.
Q.What's your favorite ingredient in a hot pot? A.Tofu.
Q.What is your favorite oden ingredient? A. Mochi-filled purse.
Who do you admire?
Who do you admire?Who do you admire?
There are many, but Mei Nagano
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island...
Oh no...
I wonder.
Hmmm...
Mm-hmm.
Whatever. What kind of water do you want? Whatever. Water?
Q. If you were going to a desert island, who would you take with you?
Waka-chan? She seems like a good survivor.
No disrespect intended.
Q.Who would you take with you to LKR?
Miu-chan, she's always been cute.
If you were a man, who would you like to date? Eh, everyone.
What sport would you like to play? Baseball!
What would make you the best dancer in the world? The best singer in the world?
Either one is fine, but I think singing.
Be the tallest person I want to be? No weight gain for life? Which do you prefer?
No weight gain for life.
What would you like to say to the newbies?
I'm always supported by all the newbies. Thanks for your support!
What song would you recommend to natives?
Wazato Azuta Expert.
What time do you go to bed and wake up?
I go to bed around 2:00 and wake up around 9:00.
What do you wear to bed?
Pajamas.
If I lived in a city, I'd live in a city.
I have red eyes.
I'd like to change it.
Why the most expensive purchase?
A. Myself. I don't spend a lot of money on expensive things, so I guess it's really clothes.
Q. What is your scariest experience? I don't know...when I went on a school trip.
When I was on a school trip, there was a girl standing on the wall wearing a white one-piece earring.
I heard from my sister that there was a girl with one white earring standing on the wall.
My sister told me about a girl with white earrings standing on the wall.
What is your favorite onigiri?What is your favorite onigiri ingredient?
Well, I like anything.
Hmmm...
How much?
What's your favorite kind of quicksilver job?
13 or something like that.
Do you want to seed the watermelon first?
Yes, I do.
Is there anything you believed in when you were little that you don't think about now?
When you were little?
You know, I don't know.
I believed in everything,
I thought I could be a Pretty Cure.
Q. How many questions are you asking now? I thought I could be Precure.
How many questions are you on? Uh, about the 50th question.
68?
What were you like when you were little?
You know, I really didn't like scary things.
I don't know what that was.
I couldn't even smooth the floor by myself.
Water or tea? Or tea? I'm a tea drinker.
Yay!
Well, I want to make a mature song. The lyrics should also be mature.
There are many karaoke boxes
There are a lot of them.
Maybe Mr. Worklock's Bellwether.
What are you doing the moment you ring in the New Year?
I'm going to eat soba (buckwheat noodles).
Scooch time, please.
Scratch time, please.
Okay, that's it.
How are you doing? I'm sleeping... because I get carsick.
What do you always order when you watch a movie?
Caramel popcorn and iced coffee.
The side dish is a grain of water.
What's the hardest song you've ever played?
Let's see...the humming of a song called "Futari no Ansatsu.
How did you get into show business?How did you get into show business?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know, but I think it was my mom's recommendation.
Do you believe in fate? I do.
Who is your favorite YouTuber?
Well, I like the Pol Pol family.
Who is your favorite YouTuber? Um, I like PolPol Family.
What were you addicted to when you were little?
When I was little?
I really loved Precure when I was little.
What's your favorite thing about you?
Well, all of them.
I have big hands.
That's my guess.
My hobbies are manga and watching movies.
I confess to being a pine needle. You're asking about that kind of love?
Matsuba, this is embarrassing.
I'm not good at night dives.
Where would you like to go in Inagi gunna? Well, there are many places. I want to go abroad.
Do you prefer Japanese food? Western food? I prefer Western food.
If you could only eat the same food in the future, what would you do?
Well, I would eat rice.
White rice.
What venue would you like to perform at?
Budokan. Budokan.
How would you compare yourself to an animal?
I want to be a bear, so I am a bear.
Wow, that's a long story.
I'll take a tweet from the last time I was here.
Let's see...
But everyone's so lively.
Hey, bear.
I hope you're not mad at me for being mad at you.
What's the one word that's lower than "lockdown"?
I don't know... one word is better than lockdown.
What is it? I think it's "unprecedented. It doesn't mean anything else.
Oh, really? The lyrics I'd like to script are by Mowglock.
Oh, you want to do it, Albert? Well, I wonder...Eh, you want to do it, Albert? Uh, I don't know...
I'd like to clean up the end of the line or something.
My favorite candy is chocolate.
What is your favorite part?
I like all of them!
Laboo.
What would you like to see fixed?
Uh, nothing in particular.
Well, maybe nothing in particular.
I love it!
No, no, no, I just said that.
No, no, no, I mean, go ahead.
I like Mick Love.
What is your ultimate goal as Mr. Tork?
Final?
Hmmm...final?
That's a difficult question to answer.
The end.
The end, right?
Eh... The last episode. The last, right?
To perform live in a big venue.
Lastly, a word of love to Tokusan Fair.
I'm always supported by you all.
I wish you all the best in the future.
I have finished answering 100 questions.
I hope you have gotten to know me better now.
Thank you so much for watching until the end.
So, please keep in touch with me.
Bye bye! ♪♪